(Howard:)He's just decided
he's never leaving his apartment again.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Brilliant.
I've been itching to pull that trigger.
(Howard:)He's upset because
he can't get anywhere with women.
(Sheldon:)Would it help if I gave him some pointers?
I'm just funning you. Ha, ha.
(Girl:)Hi. I don't know if you remember me
but I was here the other night at your party.
(Stuart:)Oh, yeah, you left with Raj.
(Sheldon:)- Yeah.
- You're the one?
(Howard:)Let me tell you something.
(Howard:)That guy you blew off
happens to be my best friend.
(Howard:)Okay? He was devastated.
(Penny:)Sorry.
(Girl:)Can you just give him this?
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Howard:)But I gotta warn you,
Raj is a proud, passionate man.
(Howard:)If you go running out on him again...
(Howard:)...you're only gonna get like three or four
more chances before you are history.